Hello everyone, this is Mizuki Yamashita.
Today, we have a solo sauna tour.
What's this?
It's Mr. Tune.
I'm sorry, Mr. Tune. I'm here at Solo Sauna, Mr. Tune. I went to Solo Sauna with Mizuki Yamashita.
I always go to Solo Sauna with my friends.
I've always gone to Solo Sauna with friends, but this is my first time alone.
I'm very excited to go to the solo sauna. This is Mr. Tune. Mr. Tune, I'm going to go.
Wow.
I feel so alone. You're sweating like a pig.
Forget it. Let's just go to sleep and not worry about cameras and stuff.
That's great.
Thank you for having me.
It looks like a stylish café.
There are some customers here.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Thank you.
Yes, please.
This looks like a curtain.
This is Mr. Chun.
Chung.
It's not a smiley face.
Mr. Chung.
When you pass through the brick...
Oh!
Oh, this is the room I'm about to enter, I'd like to enter.
please?
Wow, so beautiful
Wow
Oh, wow.
I'll take off my mask.
I'm not wearing any makeup today.
I always wear only my lips without makeup.
When I'm in the sauna, I get terribly terribly terribly terribly terribly terribly terribly terribly.
Nothing.
You know what I mean?
I'm not wearing any makeup.
And it's only 10 a.m. today.
This is also my first morning sauna.
Morning cutlet!
Anyway, I'd like to change my clothes.
After I change, I'll show you some of the things I'm going to do.
Please wait for me.
I can't show you what I'm going to change into.
Okay, now it's time for Mizuki Enoshita to change.
I just took off my coat.
Don't imagine what it's like.
Do you see it?
Look at her socks.
The staff laughed so hard at my socks.
You're supposed to wear them like this.
I want to take my socks off.
I'd like to take them off with my mouth.
I'd like to take my socks off
I'd like to take them off with my mouth
Yes, so
I've finished changing my clothes
This Mr. Tune's
From my point of view, it looks like a tuna
Sauna hat is
It's important.
You should do it. It won't hurt your hair.
It won't hurt your hair or anything.
And this is a poncho.
I think it's called a sauna poncho.
I don't know what it's called, but it's got a toweling lining.
It absorbs sweat.
Like this.
And inside is a bathing suit.
I also got some water!
Such stylish water!
Thank you very much!
And also
Even though it's a solo sauna, there are 3 chairs!
This is something...
One of the three chairs
I think it's like a Dawn.
I wonder why there are three chairs in a solo sauna.
And this is
This is a water bath.
is this one.
It's a shower room.
And a shower room.
It can be adjusted in 3 levels.
Mist is also available.
I'm so happy!
And on the top...
There's also a shower that comes down from above
There is also a shower that falls down from above.
This one seems to be the biggest size!
This is a proof of the kindness of the YouTube team, who prepared this shower because they thought it would be too dark when entering the sauna.
So now that everything is ready, I'd like to go into the sauna now!
I'm so happy!
The timer I usually use is 9 minutes.
and I'm in there for about 3 or 4 sets.
I don't know about that in general.
Okay, I'm going in.
B
Start.
Up.
Oh, it's a sauna.
Wow, it's hot.
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
Wow, it's fun! There's even a lorrie.
Look, there's a lolly. I can't see.
It's too dark... it's too dark... it's too early for me to do the lolly, so...
A little bit more, a little bit more, this way too. Hello.
I'm so embarrassed... but there's an hourglass... and I'm so happy... because it's an hourglass... and I'm so grateful to have an hourglass in the sauna... as usual.
The best thing about this sauna is... it's all good... but you can sleep.
You can touch something, sit like this, and... Oh, no, the camera fell out. The camera fell out.
We have an emergency, because less than a minute after I went into the sauna, the other camera broke.
Oh, my God, that's great! It's nice, isn't it?
No, it's nice, but...
What should I say in a sauna by myself?
The sauna I usually go to has a TV, so I watch TV.
But I can't hear the sound, so I can't talk.
I'd rather talk in the sauna than go out to eat.
We can talk in silence.
I don't know if that's the right word.
I feel like I can talk properly.
I'm starting to wonder if I'm going to be able to keep it up.
I don't know if I can handle it.
Oh, and here's my GoPro.
Oh, hey!
I feel safer with the GoPro!
Oh, but I'm getting a little hot.
Can you see my face is red?
I'm starting to sweat inside.
I have a very slow metabolism.
I'm cold, and I'm totally cold.
My toes are still cold.
I guess...
But there are more and more fashionable sauna places...
Oh, it's been 9 minutes!
He's beeping.
It's beep-beep-beep-beep!
Wow, it was beep-beep-beep!
Hey, there.
It's been 9 minutes and I'm out.
And now I'm going to take a water bath.
And I'm sweating down my nose.
Yes, sir.
I don't know if it's okay.
I'm not sure if it's okay to show this.
Well, you know, I'm going to have them cut off
I'm going to have them cut it off.
We can't show the shower scene.
So, you know...
Please enjoy the nose field footage.Enjoy the video of the nose field!
Which way? Which way is it?
Which way does it look?
Oh, here it comes!
It's cold!
Cold!
Argh!
How do I adjust this?
I'm going to run you under cold water, so you have to do some movements inside.
Oh, this, this!
Aaah!
Wrong, wrong, wrong!
It came out the top.
Oh, no!
Aaah!
Shut up!
He said he could make this thing misspelled,
You can't do Shabbos.
It's cold.
It's so cold, I can't do it.
Aaaaah!
Okay, so...
I took a water bath.
It was cold. I don't like water baths.
I don't sweat much, so after one sauna or so...
My metabolism is a little bit slow.
I would like to drink some water.
Water is important. If I don't drink water, I will collapse.
Bon appétit!
Yum! Delicious.
Yum.
Wow!
I love this chair in this sauna.
I can sleep in it.
I'm so sleepy... it's been too much of a morning.
I'm all set.
Let's go in.
Can I go in now?
Just for a second round.
I'm off.
I think you all need to get some rest.
I have special training.
I'm going in.
Let's go.
I'm going to try to sleep.
Wow!
If I sleep, I can go in for life.
I've been in the sauna since this morning.
I'm just lounging around.
I'm working.
That's great.
Mmm-hmm.
What are you looking at?
Oh, man.
Oh, my God.
Here we go.
What's this footage?
Oh, my God.
Is this really...
I wonder if this is really what all the Nogizaka fans are looking for.
I wonder if it's okay.
It's nice.
You really don't sweat.
Can you tell?
It's too dark to tell.
Hmm.
You really don't sweat.
Well, I don't want to just talk about saunas.
I'd like to talk about many things.
Recently, I'd like to give you a status report.
I have a habit of giving status reports all the time.
Every time I do, I get scolded by my mom on line.
Ha ha!
She'll get mad at me and say, "Here's what's going on...".
I'm in Basra right now.
I think it will be over by the time this is distributed.
It's going to be in 3 days or something.
Oh no!
I've been working on it since the beginning of January.
We started rehearsals about a week after the start of January.
I had to shoot two dramas in January.
I had to shoot two dramas and do some personal work.
So I was pretty busy.
I couldn't participate in the rehearsals.
I'm in a big hurry right now.
But yesterday, I saw Minami Umezawa in a play called "Kingnam".
"King Nam", which is also a teigeki play.
It was really cool.
When I see my classmates performing in a play and seeing how hard they work...
I'm like, "Wow, they're working so hard, I have to work hard, too.
Like that.
That's the kind of thing that inspires me, like Rechan.
Oh, you're sweating a lot.
I was sweating under my nose.
I don't sweat too much from my neck and forehead.
But you're sweating under your nose.
Isn't that rare? Like this.
It's a knee-sweater!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I love it!
It's so warm, and I've cranked up the bangs.
I think it was last week or something.
Hey, the auditions finally started...
21 years?
Yeah, they started in the fall of 2021.
And then in 2022...
I started taking lessons in Kansai dialect and other preparations.
We cranked the film in April.
We filmed for about 10 months, going back and forth to Osaka every day.
I wonder how many times we took the Shinkansen.
I wonder how many times I rode the Shinkansen.
I like the window seat of a three-seater the best.
I always wished I could get that seat.
I always wished I could get that seat, but in the end I fell asleep in the aisle seat because of the filming.
I have a lot of memories.
So, I got the second turn of the show...
Well, about this much...
Is this sweat?
It's not acne, is it?
It's sweat.
I'm sweating a little on my nose, too.
I'm sweating a lot like this.
What do you think?
This is the beginning of the game.
It's like a game from this point on.
So I'm going to go to the water bath.
Oh, it's cold!
Oh, it's cold.
Oh, it's cold
Feels good already
It feels better than before.
Oh, it's cold
Oh, I knew I couldn't go from my knees.
Oh, man.
I'm gonna have a baby.
Oh, no.
If you take out the reinforcement...
I feel like I'm on vacation.
Oh, wow.
But isn't your face getting better?
No... no... no... no... no... no... no... no...
That's not what I meant.
You have a post-Sanaa look, don't you?
It's a little more refreshed now, don't you think?
I don't know.
It's cool.
This picture makes me feel like I'm alone.
I want you to put something here in white, like TV Chidori's font.
I want it to look like THE loneliness.
I'm thinking of doing Laurio.I'm thinking of doing Laurio.
I'm afraid that the moment I do Laurio, all the cameras will explode.
I'm really scared.
Enjoy the sound and all!
ASMR
Here's your water.
Here we go!
I like it.
I was just saying that sound.
I was like, "Oh, my God!" when I put it in.
I wanted you to hear the sound.
Wow, it's pretty warm.
It's warm, but I want more.
That's good, I'll leave it at this level.
Wow, not at all!
My breath is already hot.
This line of the nose is magma.
It's so hot that there's probably magma flowing here right now.
Wow, but it's great!
That's a nice thunder.
I probably look like an idiot right now.
I had a reading done at that job the other day.
He said I was an idiot.
I'm an idiot on the inside.
That's great.
What a free time!
This is what I call "me time" for myself.
I've had enough.
Let's just go to bed and not worry about cameras and stuff.
Wow, I'm working up a good sweat.
Hmm?
Great, huh?
Here you go.
Wow, I'm sweating good.
Look at you. You're sweating.
You're sweating.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
You're sweating like crazy.
That's good.
Okay, so here's what happened.
My face is sweating so much.
How do you feel?
Do you feel refreshed?
But it's okay.
Wipe all the sweat off your face
But really...
I know many of you have never been to a sauna.
but it feels so good.
I hope you all go there!
I'm going to go to Vague Water after this.
I can really get a good night's sleep.
If you want to get a good night's sleep, you should go to a sauna.
Let's go to sauna!
This is Mizuki Yamashita.
Thank you very much.
Please give us a high rating, click the "Good" button, and subscribe to our channel!